gatherhere.com 2019-05-20

# Privacy Policy - Gather

* * *

This Privacy Policy describes the information that we, Gather (Gather Technologies, Inc.), collect, the ways in which we collect that information, and what we do with it. If you have any questions concerning this policy, please contact us as indicated in the How to Contact Us section below. We may update this policy from time to time, so please check this policy periodically for changes. 

## Your Information

We may collect two basic types of information, personal information and anonymous information — and we may use personal and anonymous information to create a third type of information — aggregate information. Personal and anonymous information may be collected directly from our users and prospective users, including when our users or prospective users communicate with us, create user accounts, and/or transact with us through our website located at GatherHere.com (our “site”). We define “personal information” as information that is unique to an individual. Personal information might include the following: your name, age, mailing address, zip code, contact information, and demographic information. We may collect certain information (e.g., name or gender) actively from users within our site and other information passively (e.g., ip address). We will update your information whenever we can to keep it current, accurate and complete.

## Our Use of Your Information

If we do collect your personal information, we will only use it for the purposes stated when the information was collected and as described further in this policy.

We will not sell, license, transmit or disclose your personal information outside of Gather Technologies unless:

  1. you expressly authorize us to do so;
  2. the disclosure is necessary to allow our service providers or agents to provide services for us;
  3. the disclosure is necessary in order to contact you or for us to provide our products or services to you;
  4. subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, the information is disclosed to entities that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other entities with whom we have joint marketing agreements;
  5. subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, the disclosure is in connection with a sale of all or substantially all of our assets or the merger of Gather Technologies into another entity, or any consolidation, share exchange, combination, reorganization, or like transaction in which Gather Technologies is not the survivor;
  6. disclosure is necessary in connection with other business purposes including, without limitation, customer care, service quality, business management and operation, risk assessment, security, fraud and crime prevention/detection, monitoring, research and analysis, marketing, customer purchasing preferences and trends, dispute resolution, credit checking and debt collection; or
  7. otherwise as we are required or permitted by law.

We may also use personal information to prepare aggregate information, such demographic statistics. We may share this aggregate information with our merchant partners or for other business purposes.

If you are a California resident, you may ask us to refrain from sharing your personal information (whether collected online or offline) with third parties for their marketing purposes. Please tell us your preference by contacting us as indicated in the “How to Contact Us” section of this policy below.

If you do not agree to Our Use of Your Information above, you may not use our services. Your continued use of our site constitutes your acceptance of this policy.

## Contests, Sweepstakes and Other Promotions

On our site, you may wish to participate in contests, sweepstakes and other promotions that we may offer from time to time. Through these promotions, you may choose to participate in activities such as sharing information found on our site with others and sending email invitations. In connection with any contests, sweepstakes and other promotions that we may offer from time to time via the site, we use the information you provide to administer the contests, sweepstakes and other promotions. Subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, we also may use the information to communicate with you, or the other people you select, about our products and services or our partners may use such information to communicate with you about the contests, sweepstakes or other promotions or their products and services. If you choose to participate in these promotions, and are eligible to do so, we may ask you for information such as your name, email address, date of birth and telephone number.

## Direct Marketing Material

Subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, we may from time to time contact you with information on offers of goods and services, new products and forthcoming events from us and our partners. Our site may be configured to so that your default preference is to receive these communications, however you may change your preference at any time. Please see “Your Rights” below.

## e-mail

We appreciate your questions and comments about Gather Technologies and its products and services. Please see the “How to Contact Us” section of this policy for instructions on how to send your questions and comments to us. We will share your messages with those within our organization who are most capable of addressing the issues contained in your message. We will keep a copy of your message until we have had an opportunity to address your concerns. We may archive your message for a certain period of time or discard it once it is no longer needed.

## Your Rights

You have the right to ask in writing not to receive direct marketing material from us. You can change your preferences by contacting us (see “How to Contact Us” below). Please allow us a reasonable period of time to satisfy your request.

## Cookies

We may use “cookies” on our website. Cookies allow us to identify your computer or mobile device, but not you personally. You can set your web browser to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to enjoy access and use all of the services available to you on our site. We may use cookies to customize your site experience and to send you personalized communications. We may also use cookies to keep track of session information as you move from page to page on our site and to store your preferences and personal information for the next time you visit our site.

We may also collect information relating to user trends and patterns and use cookies and software tools to measure site usage and related information.

In some cases, we may retain both cookie information and/or the information you provide to us online – for example, to complete a request or to keep historical records of your past activities. In other cases, we only retain the cookie and/or online information you give us if you request us to do so for your use in subsequent sessions.

## IP Addresses

An Internet Protocol (“IP”) address is a unique identifier that certain electronic devices use to identify and communicate with each other on the Internet. When you visit our site, we may view the IP address and host name of the device you use to connect to the Internet. We use this information to determine the general physical location of the device and understand from what regions of the world our site visitors are originating from. We also may use this information to enhance our site.

## Tracking

Our site may use “web beacons” (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags and clear GIFs). These web beacons allow third parties to obtain information such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, the type of browser used to view the page, and the information in cookies set by the third party.

## Children

Our site is a general audience website, and we do not knowingly collect information about children or provide services to children. Our site is not designed to attract anyone under the age of 18.

## Security

We have taken reasonable steps and have in place appropriate security measures to protect your personal information. You acknowledge, however, that no transmission of data over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, despite our efforts. Thus, while we will use commercially reasonable means possible to ensure the security of information you transmit to us, we cannot guarantee that such information will not be intercepted by third parties.

## Foreign Visitors

If you are visiting our site from outside of the United States or otherwise contacting us from outside of the United States, please be aware that your personal information may be transferred to, stored or processed in the United State. The data protection and other laws of the United States might not be as comprehensive as those in your country, but please be assured that we take steps to protect your privacy. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this policy.

## Links

For your convenience, we may provide links to other websites and web pages that we do not control. We cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of any websites or pages not under our control and we do not endorse any of these websites or pages, the services or products described or offered on such sites or pages, or any of the content contained on those sites or pages.

## Changes to this Policy

We may change this policy at any time. Any changes to this policy will be posted on our site. The date below indicates the most recent revision. This policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal right in or on behalf of any party.

## How To Contact Us

you have any questions about this policy or would like to learn more about how we protect privacy, please contact us by e-mail at: [theteam@gatherhere.com](mailto:theteam@gatherhere.com)

**Last updated: August 19, 2013.**
